<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<textfields file="sco_ecas_0119_1.swf" language="en">
<tf desc="mc" ref="1" fs="13" x="283.8" y="135.5" wi="377.2" he="52.5">
Pressurizing and venting the supporting and the lifting bellows is performed using a single valve block for the rear axle and the lifting axle.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="2" fs="13" x="283.8" y="205.4" wi="372.1" he="51.5">
Before the lifting axle can be raised using the RAISE button of the ECAS remote-control unit both supporting bellows of the lifting have to be completely vented.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="3" fs="13" x="283.85" y="276.5" wi="384.1" he="51.5">
When the lifting axle is raised, the pressure in the supporting bellows of the back axles remains the same, because the load weight is unchanged.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="4" fs="13" x="283.85" y="347.5" wi="352.1" he="53.95">
For a fully automated lifting axle control, triggered by the load weight, a pressure sensor connected to the supporting bellows of the main axle is required.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="8" fs="12" x="252.5" y="417.5" wi="198.05" he="21">
Confirm your selection with</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="10" fs="13" x="251.25" y="454.5" wi="61.95" he="24">
[ Ready ]</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="21" fs="13" x="252.85" y="77" wi="421.95" he="43">
This three-axle semitrailer is equipped with a lifting axle.
Which of the following statements are correct?</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="fb1" fs="13" x="1002.45" y="36.8" wi="362" he="68">
This statement is correct. The suspension bellows are pressurized or vented as well as the lifting axle is raised or lowered using this single valve block. When doing the latter, the supporting bellows of the lifting axle are pneumatically separated from those of the back axles.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="fb2" fs="13" x="1002.45" y="114.85" wi="311" he="51.5">
This statement is wrong. The supporting bellows of the lifting axle are simultaneously and automatically vented.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="fb3" fs="13" x="1002.45" y="187.85" wi="364" he="68">
This is wrong. The pressure in the supporting bellows of the back axles is increased, because the weight load is now distributed on 2 axles instead on 3. In addition the weight of the raised lifting axle is applied.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="fb4" fs="13" x="1003.45" y="293.85" wi="372" he="39">
This statement is correct. A fully automated lifting axle control is triggered be the pressure in the supporting bellows of the main axle.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="fb5" fs="13" x="1002.45" y="-18.15" wi="347" he="24">
Right, you marked all correct statements.</tf>
</textfields>