<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<textfields file="sco_ecas_0113_1.swf" language="en">
<tf desc="mc" ref="1" fs="13" x="189.85" y="145.5" wi="358.15" he="52.5">
Even before the load platform leaves the reference level ECAS starts to control, to work against the lowering caused by the load weight.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="2" fs="13" x="189.85" y="216.4" wi="377.95" he="35">
The ECAS ECU detects via the height sensors on the front and rear axles, where the reference level has been exited.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="3" fs="13" x="189.85" y="270.5" wi="399.1" he="36">
The supporting bellows on the front and the rear axle are always jointly pressurized to equally readjust the reference level.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="4" fs="13" x="189.85" y="324.5" wi="369.15" he="53.5">
The supporting bellows on two sides of an axle with 2 height sensors can be separately pressurized. In this way the reference level can be apartly readjusted after loading.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="8" fs="12" x="158.5" y="415.5" wi="198.05" he="21">
Confirm your selection with</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="10" fs="13" x="157.25" y="452.5" wi="61.95" he="24">
[ Ready ]</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="21" fs="13" x="158.85" y="85" wi="421.15" he="44">
A motor vehicle (4x2 full air) is loaded. Which of the following statements about the ECAS control processes during loading are correct?</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="fb1" fs="13" x="1002.45" y="36.8" wi="367" he="51.5">
This statement is wrong. As long as none of the height sensors has detected that the reference level has been exited, no control is performed.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="fb2" fs="13" x="1002.45" y="104.85" wi="425" he="44">
This statement is correct. When having a 4x2 full air variant the front and the rear axle are equipped with height sensors to measure the actual level.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="fb3" fs="13" x="1002.45" y="187.85" wi="375" he="39">
This statement is wrong. The bellows of the front and the rear axle can be separately pressurized.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="fb4" fs="13" x="1002.45" y="258.85" wi="279" he="37">
This statement is true. On this axle a 2-point control is applied.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="fb5" fs="13" x="1002.45" y="-18.15" wi="310" he="25">
Right, you marked the correct statement.</tf>
</textfields>