<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<textfields file="sco_ecas_0140_1.swf" language="en">
<tf desc="mc" ref="1" fs="13" x="189.85" y="139.5" wi="324.15" he="21.5">
Ensure that no one can trip over the diagnostic cable.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="2" fs="13" x="189.85" y="174.5" wi="347.15" he="37.5">
During diagnosis no one should come closer to the vehicle, since it could uncontrolledly move.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="3" fs="13" x="189.85" y="223.5" wi="355.15" he="40.5">
Measurings during calibration should be performed always from the workshop pit, never from the vehicle side.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="4" fs="13" x="189.85" y="272.5" wi="321.15" he="53.5">
When controlling compontents for testing purposes during diagnosis, it has to be ensured, that sufficient free space is available in all directions.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="5" fs="13" x="189.85" y="339.5" wi="314.15" he="53.5">
Because during ECAS diagnosis movements of the superstructure are triggered, it has to be ensured, that persons near to the vehicle cannot be crushed.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="8" fs="12" x="158.5" y="418.5" wi="224.05" he="22">
Confirm your selection with</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="10" fs="13" x="157.25" y="455.5" wi="61.95" he="24">
[ Ready ]</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="21" fs="13" x="158.85" y="77" wi="399.15" he="36">
Which of the following statements about required safety precautions during PC diagnosis of an ECAS system are correct?</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="fb1" fs="13" x="976.45" y="54.85" wi="357" he="39">
This essential precaution in everyday live is also important during diagnosis, especially near the workshop pit.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="fb2" fs="13" x="976.45" y="107.85" wi="395" he="51.5">
That would be overstated. During some diagnostic operations, e.g. when calibrating the height sensors,  simultanuous operating near to the vehice is even required.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="fb3" fs="13" x="976.45" y="175.85" wi="356" he="37">
This statement is correct. Because the superstructure can be lowered operating from the vehicle side is too dangerous.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="fb4" fs="13" x="976.45" y="231.85" wi="361" he="41">
This statement is correct. The superstructure could ram something during raising, or touch down during lowering.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="fb5" fs="13" x="976.45" y="285.85" wi="323" he="35">
This statement is true. Mainly during lowering fingers can be crushed or even sheared.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="fb6" fs="13" x="976.45" y="-0.15" wi="344" he="21">
Right, you marked the required measures.</tf>
</textfields>