<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<textfields file="sco_ecas_0145_1.swf" language="en">
<tf desc="mc" ref="2" fs="13" x="530.5" y="76" wi="151.5" he="73">
In the main window the most important data of the connected ECAS ECU is displayed.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="3" fs="12" x="38.5" y="423.5" wi="471.1" he="26">
Please move the mouse over the regions of the main window!</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="314" fs="13" x="224" y="142.25" wi="258.3" he="25">
ECU data</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="315" fs="13" x="224" y="142.25" wi="258.3" he="25">
Current note</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="316" fs="13" x="224" y="142.25" wi="258.3" he="25">
Configuration</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="317" fs="13" x="256" y="314.25" wi="303.35" he="21">
Configuration scheme (TECAS variant only)</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="319" fs="13" x="310.45" y="272.55" wi="246.3" he="22">
Status line</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="320" fs="13" x="224" y="142.25" wi="258.3" he="25">
Menue</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="321" fs="13" x="224" y="142.25" wi="258.3" he="25">
Toolbar</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="414" fs="13" x="224" y="171.25" wi="252.1" he="95.75">
In this area the individual properties of the connected ECU are displayed. Using this data you can refer to your specific device or software version when requesting the WABCO customer support.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="415" fs="13" x="224" y="171.25" wi="239.2" he="58.75">
If in the ECU one or more current faults are stored, the latest detected fault is displayed in this area.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="416" fs="13" x="224" y="171.25" wi="235.2" he="76.75">
Here you can see the configuration of the ECAS system, e.g. the number and the application positions of the height sensors and the number of lifting axles.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="417" fs="13" x="256" y="343.25" wi="308.35" he="101.95">
In the Trailer ECAS diagnostic software the ECAS configuration is graphically displayed.

The motor vehicle variants of the diagnostic software display a picture of ECAS system components at this place.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="419" fs="13" x="310.45" y="301.55" wi="281.3" he="60">
A green symbol indicates, that the data connection has been successfully established, otherwise the symbol is red.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="420" fs="13" x="224" y="171.25" wi="247.1" he="122.75">
Via the menu commands the related diagnostic functions are performed, including commissioning of the vehicle, treatment of messages, actuation of connected components for testing, measurement of values and setting of parameters.</tf>
<tf desc="mc" ref="421" fs="13" x="224" y="171.25" wi="252.05" he="41.75">
Instead of using the menu commands it is quicker to use these icons.</tf>
<obj desc="mc" ref="219" x="295.45" y="257.55" wi="308.55" he="134.45"/>
<obj desc="mc" ref="217" x="241" y="299.25" wi="355" he="170.75"/>
</textfields>